

OWNER / DIRECTOR

Details

22b Hereford street, Cape Town, 7700, South Africa +27 72 380 7335 davdmiller@icloud.com

NATIONALITY

South African / British

DRIVING LICENSE

YES

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

1984/06/16 South Africa

Links

linkedin

twitter

<u>GitHub</u>

Skills

HTML & CSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript

Wordpress

MongoDB

Express.js

React.js

Node.js

Profile

Owner of Video Image Technologies with a demonstrated history of working in the film and media production industry. I am a web developer. I love coding, designing functional websites. I'm skilled in Research, MERN Stack, Node.js, JavaScript, and Digital Video. Strong business development professional who graduated from Cape Audio College in 2004.

Employment History

Owner, Video Image Technologies, Cape Town

AUGUST 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2020

DIT and VTO specialist for media and film

Humerous Music, Self Employed, Cape Town

FEBRUARY 2009 - OCTOBER 2016

Dj / Producer at Humerous Music

Bartender, Cafe Caprice, Cape Town

JUNE 2004 - JULY 2009

Food and Drink server.

SEPTEMBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

Education

Certified , Full-stack developer , 6 months online course , Hyperion Development, Cape Town

MAY 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020

Sound Engineering Diploma, Cape Audio College, Cape Town

JANUARY 2003 - DECEMBER 2004

High School Diploma, Boston House College, Cape Town

JANUARY 2020 - DECEMBER 2002

High School Diploma, Camps Bay High School, Cape Town

JANUARY 1997 - DECEMBER 1999

Primary School Diploma, Camps Bay Primary School, Cape Town

JANUARY 1991 - DECEMBER 1996

References

Sobane Motlomelo from Hyperion Developement

sobanem@hyperiondev.com | +27 73 705 2680

Mark van der Merve from Onset Post

mark@onsetpost.co.za | +27 73 166 5910

Courses

Certified , Full-stack developer , 6 months online course , Hyperion Developement

MAY 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020

The complete web development bootcamp, Udemy

MAY 2019 - AUGUST 2019

